#### Contact

rosamariabado@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rosita-bado-454364a0 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Career Development Hospitals Healthcare

# Rosita Bado

Operating Room Nurse at St. Vincent's HealthCare Georgetown, Texas

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Career Development, Medical-Surgical, U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), Team Building, and Public Speaking. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Texas State University.

# Experience

St. Vincent's HealthCare
Operating Room Nurse
April 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)
Montana

LRS Healthcare Registered Nurse November 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months) Billings, Montana

Travel Nurse

St. David's HealthCare
Registered Nurse
September 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 1 month)
Georgetown, Texas

Scott and White Baylor
Registered Nurse
July 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 3 months)
Temple, Texas

## Education

# Texas State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2012 - 2014)

## University of North Texas

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Kinesiology and Exercise Science · (2007 - 2011)